{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "ja",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "a",
      "answer": "ア"
    },
    {
      "question": "e",
      "answer": "エ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ka",
      "answer": "カ"
    },
    {
      "question": "i",
      "answer": "イ"
    },
    {
      "question": "u",
      "answer": "ウ"
    },
    {
      "question": "o",
      "answer": "オ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ku",
      "answer": "ク"
    },
    {
      "question": "ke",
      "answer": "ケ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ko",
      "answer": "コ"
    },
    {
      "question": "sa",
      "answer": "サ"
    },
    {
      "question": "shi",
      "answer": "シ"
    },
    {
      "question": "su",
      "answer": "ス"
    },
    {
      "question": "se",
      "answer": "セ"
    },
    {
      "question": "so",
      "answer": "ソ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ta",
      "answer": "タ"
    },
    {
      "question": "chi",
      "answer": "チ"
    },
    {
      "question": "tsu",
      "answer": "ツ"
    },
    {
      "question": "te",
      "answer": "テ"
    },
    {
      "question": "to",
      "answer": "ト"
    },
    {
      "question": "na",
      "answer": "ナ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ni",
      "answer": "ニ"
    },
    {
      "question": "nu",
      "answer": "ヌ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ne",
      "answer": "ネ"
    },
    {
      "question": "no",
      "answer": "ノ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ha",
      "answer": "ハ"
    },
    {
      "question": "hi",
      "answer": "ヒ"
    },
    {
      "question": "fu",
      "answer": "フ"
    },
    {
      "question": "he",
      "answer": "ヘ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ho",
      "answer": "ホ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ma",
      "answer": "マ"
    },
    {
      "question": "mi",
      "answer": "ミ"
    },
    {
      "question": "mu",
      "answer": "ム"
    },
    {
      "question": "me",
      "answer": "メ"
    },
    {
      "question": "mo",
      "answer": "モ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ya",
      "answer": "ヤ"
    },
    {
      "question": "yu",
      "answer": "ユ"
    },
    {
      "question": "yo",
      "answer": "ヨ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ra",
      "answer": "ラ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ri",
      "answer": "リ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ru",
      "answer": "ル"
    },
    {
      "question": "re",
      "answer": "レ"
    },
    {
      "question": "ro",
      "answer": "ロ"
    },
    {
      "question": "wa",
      "answer": "ワ"
    },
    {
      "question": "wo",
      "answer": "ヲ"
    },
    {
      "question": "n",
      "answer": "ン"
    },
    {
      "question": "ki",
      "answer": "キ"
    }
  ]
}
